[
  {
      "question": "لاو",
      "response": "لاو"
  },
  {
      "question": "ايس",
      "response": "ايس"
  },
  {
      "question": "لوفي",
      "response": "لوفي"
  },
  {
      "question": "نامي",
      "response": "نامي"
  },
  {
      "question": "ويليام",
      "response": "ويليام"
  },
  {
      "question": "نويل",
      "response": "نويل "
  },
  {
      "question": "استا",
      "response": "استا"
  },
  {
      "question": "ايرين",
      "response": "ايرين"
  },
  {
      "question": "يامي",
      "response": "يامي"
  },
  {
      "question": "ليفاي",
      "response": "ليفاي"
  },
  {
      "question": "ميكاسا",
      "response": "ميكاسا"
  },
  {
      "question": "نوبارا",
      "response": "نوبارا"
  },
  {
      "question": "ايتاشي",
      "response": "ايتاشي"
  },
  {
      "question": "ساسكي",
      "response": "ساسكي"
  },
  {
      "question": "بوروتو",
      "response": "بوروتو"
  },
  {
      "question": "مادارا",
      "response": "مادارا"
  },
  {
      "question": "توبي",
      "response": "توبي"
  },
  {
      "question": "اوبيتو",
      "response": "اوبيتو"
  },
  {
      "question": "كاكاشي",
      "response": "كاكاشي"
  },
  {
      "question": "كونوهامارو",
      "response": "كونوهامارو"
  },
  {
      "question": "بولاف ",
      "response": "بولاف "
  },
  {
      "question": "كيريتو   ",
      "response": "كيريتو   " 
  },
  {
      "question": "اسونا ",
      "response": "اسونا "
  },
  {
      "question": "سيباستيان ",
      "response": "سيباستيان "
  },
  {
      "question": "كورو ",
      "response": "كورو "
  },
  {
      "question": "كرولو ",
      "response": "كرولو "
  },
  {
      "question": "فيتان ",
      "response": "فيتان "
  },
  {
      "question": "غون ",
      "response": "غون "
  },
  {
      "question": "كيلوا",
      "response": "كيلوا"
  },
  {
      "question": "هينا ",
      "response": "هينا "
  },
  {
      "question": "بياكوغان ",
      "response": "بياكوغان "
  },
  {
      "question": "هيناتا ",
      "response": "هيناتا "
  },
  {
      "question": "ايرو",
      "response": "ايرو"
  },
  {
      "question": "كاغويا ",
      "response": "كاغويا "
  },
  {
      "question": "كانامي ",
      "response": "كانامي "
  },
  {
      "question": "تسوموغو ",
      "response": "تسوموغو "
  },
  {
    "question": "بيتو ",
      "response": "بيتو "
  },
  {
      "question": "كايتو ",
      "response": "كايتو "
  },
  {
      "question": "كيد ",
      "response": "كيد "
  },
  {
      "question": "كيلر ",
      "response": "كيلر "
  },
  {
      "question": "كورو سينسي",
      "response": "كورو سينسي"
  },
  {
      "question": " بولات ",
      "response": "بولات "
  },
  {
      "question": "تاتسومي ",
      "response": "تاتسومي "
  },
  {
      "question": "كارلوس ",
      "response": "كارلوس "
  },
  {
      "question": "تسوباسا ",
      "response": "تسوباسا "
  },
  {
      "question": "هيوغا ",
      "response": "هيوغا "
  },
  {
      "question": "نيجي ",
      "response": "نيجي "
  },
  {
      "question": "اينو ",
      "response": "اينو "
  },
  {
     "question": "ايليينا ",
      "response": "ايليينا "
  },
  {
     "question": "توكا ",
      "response": "توكا "
  },
  {
     "question": "توغا ",
      "response": "توغا "
  },
  {
     "question": "توايس ",
      "response": "توايس "
  },
  {
     "question": "ماين ",
      "response": "ماين "
  },
  {
     "question": "جينتل ",
      "response": "جينتل "
  },
  {
     "question": "ايلي ",
      "response": "ايلي "
  },
  {
     "question": "ايري ",
      "response": "ايري "
  },
  {
     "question": "ايليزابيث ",
      "response": "ايليزابيث "
  },
  {
     "question": "ميليوداس",
      "response": "ميليوداس"
  },
  {
     "question": "غارا ",
      "response": "غارا "
  },
  {
    "question": "ناغاتو 』",
      "response": "ناغاتو "
  },
  {
     "question": "ياهيكو ",
      "response": "ياهيكو "
  },
  {
     "question": "كونان ",
      "response": "كونان "
  },
  {
     "question": "توكيتو ",
      "response": "توكيتو "
  },
  {
     "question": "رينغوكو ",
      "response": "رينغوكو "
  },
  {
     "question": "ميتسوري ",
      "response": "ميتسوري "
  },
  {
     "question": "غيو ",
     "response": "غيو "
  },
  {
     "question": "توميوكا ",
      "response": "توميوكا "
  },
  {
     "question": "سابيتو ",
      "response": "سابيتو "
  },
  {
     "question": "ماكومو ",
      "response": "ماكومو "
  },
  {
     "question": "يوسكي ",
      "response": "يوسكي "
  },
  {
     "question": "بوسكي ",
      "response": "بوسكي "
  },
  {
     "question": "نايت اي",
      "response": "نايت اي"
   },
  {
     "question": "غيومي",
      "response": "غيومي"
   },
  {
     "question": "تانجيرو ",
      "response": "تانجيرو "
   },
  {
     "question": "يوريتشي",
      "response": "يوريتشي"
   },
  {
     "question": "سانيمي",
      "response": "سانيمي"
   },
  {
     "question": "نيزوكو ",
      "response": "نيزوكو "
   },
  {
     "question": "شادو",
      "response": "شادو"
   },
  {
     "question": "اوروكوداكي ",
      "response": "اوروكوداكي "
   },
  {
     "question": "فيلو ",
      "response": "فيلو "
   },
  {
     "question": "ناوفومي ",
      "response": "ناوفومي "
   },
  {
     "question": "كاناو ",
      "response": "كاناو "
   },
  {
     "question": "تينغن ",
      "response": "تينغن "
   },
  {
     "question": "اوروتشيمارو",
      "response": "اوروتشيمارو"
   },
  {
     "question": "رافتاليا ",
      "response": "رافتاليا "
   },
  {
     "question": "زينو ",
      "response": "زينو "
   },
  {
     "question": " سيلفر فانغ",
      "response": " سيلفر فانغ"
   },
  {
     "question": "بانغ ",
      "response": "بانغ "
   },
  {
     "question": "سويريو ",
      "response": "سويريو "
   },
  {
     "question": "غارو ",
      "response": "غارو "
   },
  {
     "question": "باتمان ",
      "response": "باتمان "
   },
  {
     "question": "جوكر ",
      "response": "جوكر "
   },
  {
     "question": "فانيتاس ",
      "response": "فانيتاس "
   },
  {
     "question": "ياماتو",
      "response": "ياماتو"
   },
  {
     "question": "سيرا ",
      "response": "سيرا "
   },
  {
     "question": "كوزيت ",
      "response": "كوزيت "
   },
  {
     "question": "مادلين ",
      "response": "مادلين "
   },
  {
     "question": "فالجان ",
      "response": "فالجان "
   },
  {
     "question": "كورفيراك ",
      "response": "كورفيراك "
   },
  {
     "question": "انجولراس ",
      "response": "انجولراس "
   },
  {
     "question": "مايكي ",
      "response": "مايكي "
   },
  {
     "question": "سايتاما ",
      "response": "سايتاما "
   },
  {
     "question": "فودو ",
      "response": "فودو "
   },
  {
     "question": "كودو ",
      "response": "كودو "
   },
  {
     "question": "شيراهوشي ",
      "response": "شيراهوشي "
   },
  {
     "question": "هارو ",
      "response": "هارو "
   },
  {
     "question": "هاروهي ",
      "response": "هاروهي "
   },
  {
     "question": "هيكاري ",
      "response": "هيكاري "
   },
  {
     "question": "ميونا ",
      "response": "ميونا "
   },
  {
     "question": "غوجو",
      "response": "غوجو"
   },
  {
     "question": "يوغي ",
      "response": "يوغي "
   },
  {
     "question": "ايتادوري ",
      "response": "ايتادوري "
   },
  {
     "question": "ناتسو ",
      "response": "ناتسو "
   },
  {
     "question": "غراي ",
      "response": "غراي "
   },
  {
     "question": "ايرزا ",
      "response": "ايرزا "
   },
  {
     "question": "لوسي ",
      "response": "لوسي "
   },
  {
     "question": "كاناي ",
      "response": "كاناي "
   },
  {
     "question": "هابي ",
      "response": "هابي "
   },
  {
     "question": "اينو ",
      "response": "اينو "
   },
  {
     "question": "ساي ",
      "response": "ساي "
   },
  {
     "question": "ريم ",
      "response": "ريم "
   },
  {
     "question": "رام ",
      "response": "رام "
   },
  {
     "question": "بو ",
      "response": "بو "
   },
  {
     "question": "بي ",
      "response": "بي "
   },
  {
     "question": "با ",
      "response": "با "
   },
  {
     "question": "هيسوكا ",
      "response": "هيسوكا "
   },
  {
     "question": "ماتشي ",
      "response": "ماتشي "
   },
  {
     "question": "دراغون ",
      "response": "دراغون "
   },
  {
     "question": "غوكو ",
      "response": "غوكو "  
  },
  {
     "question": "ديدارا ",
      "response": "ديدارا "
   },
  {
     "question": "كورابيكا ",
      "response": "كورابيكا "
}
]
